{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834800873","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834800873"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834801426","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834801426"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834802411","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834802411"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834802984","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834802984"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834803711","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834803711"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834806316","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834806316"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834806599","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834806599"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834807289","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834807288"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834807885","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834807884"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834808745","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834808744"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834809587","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834809585"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834810020","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834810020"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834810903","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834810901"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834812262","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834812260"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834813508","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834813508"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834813520","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834813519"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834813968","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834813968"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834814550","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834814550"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834817344","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834817343"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834818126","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834818126"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834819209","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834819209"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834819833","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834819833"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834822886","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834822886"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834823178","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834823177"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834823876","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834823875"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834824121","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834824120"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834824569","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834824568"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834825232","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834825231"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834825635","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834825635"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834826618","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834826618"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834828012","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834828012"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834828516","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834828516"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834829800","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834829800"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834830625","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834830625"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834831586","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834831586"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834834201","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834834200"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" MUMEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834835406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834835406"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834836299","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834836299"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834836792","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834836792"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834837876","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834837876"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIVUNIA"," userResponse":" KUJIVUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834838580","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834838580"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834841102","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834841102"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834841865","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834841865"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834842068","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834842068"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834842651","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834842651"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834843505","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834843505"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834844649","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834844649"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834845216","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834845215"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834846290","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834846290"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWACHA"," userResponse":" ALIMWACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834846960","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834846960"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834847825","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834847825"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834848810","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834848809"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834849474","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834849473"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834850077","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834850077"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834850552","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834850552"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834851330","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834851329"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKAMA"," userResponse":" KUKAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834851863","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834851863"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834851880","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834851880"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834854554","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834854553"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834854828","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834854828"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834855635","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834855634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834856295","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834856294"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834857626","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834857625"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWACHIA"," userResponse":" KUMWACHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834858388","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834858387"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KIBUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834858634","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834858634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834859413","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834859412"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834860354","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834860353"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834861097","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834861096"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEMA"," userResponse":" PEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834862097","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834862096"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834862181","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834862181"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834862740","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834862739"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834865712","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834865711"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834866226","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834866225"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834867034","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834867034"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834867875","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834867874"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBAKI"," userResponse":" ALIBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834868724","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834868723"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" CHUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834870088","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834870088"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834870330","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834870330"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834871171","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834871170"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" KUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834871885","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834871885"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834872528","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834872528"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834873182","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834873182"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834873875","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834873874"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834874578","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834874578"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834877018","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834877018"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543834998778","data":{"timestamp":" 1543834998778"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_135943"," gameId":" 52ba5ce1-e65f-4cad-8e83-16b97bb8e7d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}